MIRROR MIRROR
Once upon a time, in a kingdom far far away
a baby girl is borned
Her skin is as pure as a snow
Her hair is as dark as the night
They called her...Snow White
Probably because that was the most pretentious name they can come out with
As faith has it, Snow White's mother died in child birth
Left on his own, her father spoiled the young girl.
he can afford to of course, he was the king.
The king loved his daughter, and all the subjects love him.
The kingdom was a happy place.
where people danced and sang day and night.
Apparently no one had a job back then.
Just singing and dancing all day and all night.
Oh my, that gross.
The king raised the little girl by himself...
Growing her to one day lead.
Over time, he realized there's some things he couldn't teach her.
So he sort out...
A new Queen
This queen was the most beautiful woman in the world
She was intelligent, and strong, and...
Just to clarify...
She was me.
And this is my story...
not her.
Bewitched by my beauty, the king begged me to marry him
I was everything to him.
The Stars, The moon...
But the dark magic invaded the land.
The brave king said farewell to Snow White
Leaving her his favorite dagger.
It's interestng gift...
But we're on that later...
He rode off into the dark woods, and sadly...
was never seen again
Snow White searched and searched her father...
And when she realized he was trully gone.She was devastated.
The girl was now left under the care of the beautiful queen...
10 years pasted, and Snow White grew older and blossomed...
But the kingdom was turned into icy despair, and the queen realized...
if she wanted to remain the most beautiful woman on the land...
Well..snow would have to what snow does best
Snow would have to fall.
Hallo, there
Would you like a treat?
Here you go
I think the party's started
F to D9.
To your left, Lord Waverly.
If someone please teach Lord Waverly his left from his right...
I would be so very grateful
- Forgive me
- B to J12.
Milady, I feel is my duties to tell you rumors that I've been hearing.
- Rumors?
- Well...
There have been rumblings that the kingdom is closed to destity.
If we were to join our two houses
by marriage,
I wil be sure to you that the kingdom will be stable once again.
Brighton, a word, please.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
- Loose lips sink ships.
Yes indeed, Your Majesty, exactly.
Which ship would you like sunk?
It is an expression, Brighton.
A royal decree. Take it down
- Marvelous.
- Any busybodies
Who is caught spreading rumors,
gossiping, whispering...
Or even thinking... shall be put to death.
How that sounds?
Decisive.
Snow White.
- Is there a fire?
-I'm Sorry?
Is your bedroom on fire?
I'm searching for explaination why you out of your bedroom.
Here..and my first guess is it was on fire.
I thought maybe I could come to the gala.
-You know because today is my 18 birthday.
- Today
Oh My...Oh My...
E to F3, please.
Snow White...
Maybe it's time I ease up on you.
Afterall, you've done nothing to me.
Cause no problems.
And yet ...
There's something about you that just so incredibly...
irritating.
But I don't know what is.
The slope shoulders...
The hair and voice...
I know what it is.
I think it's because of the hair.
I hate your hair.
I do not care if it's
your 100th birthday.
Don't ever sneak to a party like this again
B to F6.
C to D4.
Baron, you've been beaten for the last 5 minutes
and didn't even know it.
Bravo, Your Majesty!
It's important to know when you've been beaten.
Yes?
I don't like the looks of this woods, Sir..
If you don't mind me saying this, but it seems
Trees, Renbock.
Trees are just wood.
It's not the trees I'm afraid of, sir.
I heard the story of a man
eating beast inhabitant these parts.
Thrilled my heart to know when my traveler companion
still believes in fairy tales.
If you don't mind me asking this,
when is your highness going to get home?
We are on the road for months.
I thought we could perhaps take a break.
We don't sort out seeking a vacation,
we sort out seeking adventure.
- An adventure?
- And we're going to find one.
I think it's a bad idea, sir.
We should ride on
Not until we find out what's in this woods
Turn around!
- Giants!
- Renbock!
- Empty your pockets.
- What?
I said empty your pockets!
Give me that!
Down!
Stay down.
I found some road-killed.
You can see?
Do you?
Sir...
What's so funny?
You are not giant?
None of you is giant.
- And your point is?
- You expect me to fight you?
Then he can see!
- Of course he can see!
I most certainly, I will not fight against a bunch of dwarf..
- Why?
- You're menisque.
- Tiny?
- A diminutive?
- Runt?
- Thank you.
- Runt? That's the best you got?
- Nobody explained.
- And the people used to call us...
It doesn't matter.
You're short and it's funny.
Funny?
Not as funny as my blade at your throat.
Please, Back.
All we want is his gold.
- I got his wallet full.
- Now we're talking.
Let's look at it.
Come on, bring it here.
- It is not your property.
- Whatever.
- Get your hands off of it immediately!
- Give them what they want, Sir.
Where is the gold?
Out of my way.
Someone should give a lesson to these children.
No one is to know the details,Renbock.
Do you understand?
Say it!
No one needs to know the details. Your royal highness
- Happy birthday, Snow
- You remembered!
Of course we remember.
A girl 18 birthday is the most important birthday of them all.
You want to know what I wish
for your birthday, Snow White?
You can't make a wish for me.
Do you know why I keep working for the
unpleasant queen year after year?
I do it because i know one day you will going to take back your kingdom
And I want to be here when that happens.
- It's not my kingdom.
Oh..but it is
Your father meant to you to inherit his crown.
But that woman has the entire kingdom
that you are a pathetic girl,
unable to leave the castle.
And the worst is you think that you do.
Your father's dagger.
I have it cleaned and polished.
What I do with this?
Perhaps you have to see for yourself
what's going on in your kingdom.
The people don't sing and dance anymore.
They need to see who you really are.
And you need to believe.
- I'm going out.
- Is she running away?
I don't know. Is she?
Ok!
She's going out.
I won't say nothing, if
you don't say anything.
- Pinky swear?
- Pinky swear.
Mirror mirror on the wall...
Can you believe that Baron?
I mean honestly the he really think I would consider in marrying him?
Women have standards after all, and a exotic woman like myself,
have very high standards.
- Interesting.
- What?
Your response to his proposal.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- Consider the options.
The option is to receiving an heirline not some rotten eggs and
and would have to death with him.
You spend so much supporting your vanity.
And you can't afford to say no.
Why not snap your fingers and
make me a chest of gold?
Everyone has the magic within him,
but very few discover and learn to spent it wisely.
Trust me.
I'm after all only a reflection of you.
well not in exact reflection
I have no wrinkles.
They're not wrinkles.
- Just something.
- As you wish.
- What do you suggest I do?
- I suggest you marry someone rich, quickly.
Because one day soon you'll ask me
who is the fairest of them all is.
and you won't like the answer.
Hello?
- Is anybody out there?
- Shut up, Renbock!
- No one can hear you in the woods.
- Can be any passerby.
Ok, you think there is someone else in the miserable woods?
- Well, there could be.
- It's that thumb?
- No. I do not like.
- This is very clever...
I don't like being so close to you.
I said it.
Wondered what I would
find in this woods, but...
I chose the worst road companion.
I never imagine this!
We need your help,
we were ambushed by Seven Dwarfs.
- Blood trusty giants
- Giants?
We out numberded, we fought bravely
Young Lady, if you be so kind to help myself and my honourable Prince...
Friend... friend...
I am a humble commoner.
- I'm ordering you to release...
- Ordering?
If you refuse,
will bear the consequences.
Only if you say please.
Given the situation, I think please is in order.
You right.
Where are my manners?
- Please.
- That's all you had to say.
Thank you. Thank you...
Thank you so much.
No. No. No. No. No.
Please.
Are you alright?
Can I help, at all?
- Yes, Miss, untie me please
- Alright, here you go.
You want some help with the rope?
Yes, Thank you.
I am sorry to see us in an uncompromising position.
- We're going north.
- I'm heading south.
It's a shame.
Yes, it is.
I think it's time to go.
- She turn around
- No. I don't think she's interesting, Sir.
- Your Highness!
- Yes
Pardon me, Majesty, but...
You have a visitor.
I'm not in the mood, Brighton.
He is young, and handsome...
And semi-nude.
Your Highness, May I present to you...
The esteem Prince Alcott of Valencia.
Your Majesty.
The reason of my undress.
Me and my valet were robbed by bandits
at the entrance to the kingdom.
Bandits? Awful!
It is absolutely terrifying...
Smooth hair...
- What?
What?
Nothing.
Perhaps we can use some covering?
Perhaps a shirt?
If you must...
- Brighton.
- Brighton...
Your Majesty...
Prince is shy and requires, sadly, a covering.
Of course, Milady
Sir?
- Is there any particular shirt you like...?
- Brighton.
- A simple covering
- A simple covering, it is.
Valencia you said.
I've never heard of it.
- Is there a village?
- No, no, it's a quite country, Your Highness.
It is a wonderful province.
We have many natural resources.
Gold, silver, silk trade...
You don't say..
Send invitations!
Alert the caterer!
I want you to organize a ball
like this kingdom's never seen before.
We're going to sweep the chin right out of him.
Forgive me, Your Majesty, but...
I don't understand.
Brighton, the prince is rich
and strong as a bull.
I'm going to marry him, and
my financial problems will be solved.
I understand that.
What I don't understand is how
you intend to pay for the party.
Forgive me to say this, but
you're broke, My Queen.
And go and collect more taxes.
Your Majesty, I don't know when
you last time you're in the town,
but people are starving.
Don't they have imagination?
Go tell them bread is meat.
That less is more.
Ordinary people just loves good metaphors.
Just go set it!
Bread is meat.
Excuse me...
You have anything to eat?
What happened here?
I visited once with my father,
it was a great place.
People always singing and dancing.
It must have been many years ago.
- More taxes?
- Good, you could read.
- Make sure they are collected by the time I return.
- What you do with all our money?
- Protecting you.
- From what?
Must I remind the brutal attacks we have suffered?
- Attacks of...
- The Beast!
Yes, the evil lives in dark woods
more hideous than you can ever imagine.
There is only reason not to show itself in front of all of you
is because your tax had it done.
I'll be back tomorrow for the money.
You will return as quickly as possible to
our kingdom and bring a squad of guards.
Remember how you dressed, Sir.
- Go get clothes, gold and an army.
- Clothes?
Why, you don't like the queen's
taste of male fashion?
- Have you listen to nothing of what I said?
- Yes, soldiers, gold and clothes.
- Yes
- Good.
- Only if you say please.
- Please Renbock.
- Look Sir, I ask you to come with me.
This Queen radiates crazy.
You know all the women always get crazy
when a prince's around.
I notice that, but I meant there's a simple prince crazy...
... and there's a good old fashioned plain traditonal physcho crazy.
I think she's all of that.
Save trip, Renbock!
When you return, pray you're wearing your pants.
I will pray the same for you, Sir.
See you soon!
Maid Margaret!
It is worse than you could ever imagine!
- You saw the town?
- Yes, and it's awful.
Queen destroyed everything
that my father believed in.
Come on.
She takes more to them who have nothing.
That's to pay the lavish parties.
She's throwing another one tonight.
For a prince.
- A prince here?
- Snow White...
He said he have an army.
Perhaps he could help us.
If he trully have an army, then he
can help us take back the kingdom.
bisa membantu kita
menyelamatkan kerajaan ini.
Oh My Goodness, Someone tells me
you've had quite a day!
But you're going to have a bigger than that.
He said he have an army.
Perhaps he could help us.
Brighton, I haven't even begun to get ready yet.
- Then one can only imagine how much if you...
- Shut up, Brighton.
With pleasure.
- The treatment is ready.
- Treatment?
- Isn't that too excessive?
- No such thing.
I'll try.
Biting levels.
Bites bite, I bit the levels...
It's needed. it's needed.
It is always the worst.
I can feel you're smiling.
Her Majesty the Queen!
His Royal Highness the Prince of Valencia!
Folklore? Coelho is desired.
Because of his shrewdness
enough just to overcome fear.
Or perhaps you prefer that guests
do not feel comfortable, but
slightly uncomfortable.
Handsome and smart.
How confusing!
Take a turn.
- You?
- You!
- You're here?
- I am here, but...
You are the prince?
Excuse me, watching you in this dress,
I'm speechless.
Well, It didn't cost you to lose your
pants.
I mean... when I met you
first, you're not wearing pants.
- Yes
- At least now you're dressed...up.
Like a bunny.
Apparently it's a rabbit.
Something about enemies and I...
- Well
- I look like an idiots.
Yes, a little bit.
- What are...
- doing in the palace?
I live here.
I haven't for a while.
- I'm the princess.
- What?
- No one tell me that.
- No, you told me you're not a prince.
Afraid of appearing ridiculous.
- It should not change the pairs?
- Yes, I think so.
- Forgive me.
- No, no, no. it was nothing.
The truth is I didn't come here just to dance tonight.
- I need your help.
- Anything.
I am at your disposal.
It's about the queen.
Since my father died, she
terrorizes people and ruined the land.
And I Hope a good prince like yourself, could help.
I have to go.
- Brighton.
- Right away
Unworthy Creature, what are you doing
talking to my prince?
- Your Prince?
- And where did you get the dress?
You want to talk about my dress
or waht you did to the village?
Good for you, Snow White!
Someone has been taking the confidence pills.
Do it again.
Say it again. Come on.
You're not funny.
Brighton, you do it.
- Want to talk about my dress...
More anger, more infuriating!
Want to talk about my dress
or what you did the village?
- Actually, you're both are irretating.
- I've been there.
- I've seen what you did to people.
- You left the castle ground?
Snow White's  breaking all the rules today.
- Deserves a punishment for it.
- By whose law?
You have no right to rule like you do.
Technically, I'm the rightful leader of this kingdom.
Probably not the best thing that you could have said.
- I want her killed.
- Killed?
- Your Majesty isn't that a little bit rash?
- She is a threat to everything.
Take her to the woods and feed her to the beast.
Is this about the dress?
- Keep going.
- Let me go!
I swear I'll never see him again!
Do you think I want to be here?
You did this to yourself!
You shouldn't against the queen,
Now we both pay for it.
Stop.
- Brighton, please...
- Turn around.
Please...Brighton, I'm afraid.
- I do not want to die like my father.
- Your father was a good man.
He was always kind to me.
Run...Run as fast as you can,
as far away from here as possible.
Run.
- Like this!
- Brighton.
Run!
I have to invent something.
Or she won't believe me.
Brighton.
- Brighton!
- I'm coming! I'm coming...
- Your Majesty...
- Is it done?
Just as you asked.
- The liver, kidneys, spleen...
- Disgusting.
- And a few other parts...
- I admit.
I'm impressed.
You're not as pathetic as
I've always believed.
It is the nicest thing you've ever said to me.
I feel amazing!
Much lighter!
It's nice to see you such in good mood.
Yes, we must announce the tragedy, right?
Things ever...
Harvest  flowers, a terrible loss, flies the flags at half mast...
The flags throughout the kingdom or just in the palace?
It is too much trouble.
Forget the flags.
Your parts and your dagger.
- Good night!
Sleep well!
Glory!
She's a wake
- Who are you?
- We ask the questions here.
- My name is Snow White.
- Snow White?
- No way.
- Snow White is in the palace.
- Yes, she's locked in the tower.
- Maybe another Snow White.
- What?
There is a very common name.
If you are Snow White, then...
- Who is your father?
- The King
She is Snow White, you see?
I say never trust someone more than 4 ft.
Yes
Let's go back to the woods with her
and pretend we did not see anything.
- No Fools, she's the princess.
- Means that it is valuable.
- We demand a ransom.
- Can be filled with gold!
Maybe we should get to know her first.
You won't get any gold from me.
They want me dead.
The Queen sent me to be killed by the beast.
- Why the Queen wants you dead?
- Because she's wicked.
- She is evil.
- She's a witch.
Remember that time...
Sorry, but we have our appoinment to keep.
- It's time to say goodbye.
- Wait. You can't just kick me out.
- I have nowhere else to go.
- If the Queen to find you here,
She'll kill us too.
All I'm asking is to spend one night.
Please...
Assembly!
Well, guys, listen up.
Everyone agrees that the girl stay,
say "yes."
Yes
- Against?
- Me
- Bad luck, Your Highness.
- Sorry, Snow White.
The vote must be unanimous.
One night.
Thank you.
- Come on, guys, duty calls!
- Wait!
- I don't even know your names.
- I am the Butcher.
- Will Grimm.
- Half Pain.
Napoleon.
Grub.
- Chuck.
- You can call him Chuckles.
Concentration.
No more discussion.
Maybe you should stick with it.
I think you need a...
I do not.
I am the Wolf.
- Boys... I like her.
- Yeah, me too.
Bring out the feminine touch.
If you asked me, she's just going to bring the queen guards.
- Do you think she has a boyfriend?
- Yes, she is
Snow White is dead.
One of God's great mysteries is His plans.
- for each everyone of you.
- You can go.
Snow White lived and died.
God rest her soul. Amen.
It will be a buffet lunch serve at 14:00.
Magistrate, I've come for the taxes.
People can not bear this much longer.
Are seriously going to argue about that money instead of grieving?
That's odd!
- What we have here?
- I'd say it's a noble.
- You are noble?
- I'm not noble, I am just a humble servant.
You're strolling in the royal carriage.
- No, it is rental.
- You're wearing nobles clothing.
This garbage?
You guyss, must leave the woods more often.
What's in that beautiful bag?
- My lunch.
- That infamous! Let's see?
Boys, chickens are golden!
Give it here!
This money belongs to the queen!
Do not spend it all in one place
Nothing compares with an honest day's work.
It's worth the work.
Welcome home!
- Lamb, carrots, bread...
- I say let's eat.
Of course she will.
Brother!
- Thank you.
- With pleasure.
Unbelievable!
Why do you have the palace guards' uniform?
- I received at work.
- What kind of job do you have?
- We... renegades.
- Rebels.
- Thieves!
- That's true.
We took the queen's gold!
- You've broke into the palace?
- No, we stole out of the village.
- So, you actually stole the people's gold?
- Not exactly.
Of course it is
That's the people's money.
It's horrible! The need it.
- You must return it.
- I worked hard for that money.
- Stealing isn't work!
- Sure, it's work!
- It's hard!
- I stole, I have to sell it.
This is work.
I'm sorry that you have worked hard.
- But people need that money.
- They hate us.
- That can't be true.
- Yes it is. They despise us.
Years ago, when the Queen expelled undesirables
no one stood for us.
She said...
vanished out all the uglies.
You have been mistreated by the Queen.
No one understands that better than me.
It's unfair, but so with stealing from
innocent families.
- We weren't always thieves.
- I was right.
- I had a real job.
- I was a teacher.
- I was a butcher.
- I had a place.
- There were arts and crafts fair.
- Seriously.
I was almost honest.
I stole a cadiquinho anything...
- A cadiquinho?
- It's a business with money.
- That is an excuse?
- Everybody does it.
- Yes, right?
- I never did.
- Neither do I.
- Left fingerprints in the robbery.
- No!
- Yes! And the Poker!
- You cheated at poker.
- Cheated at Poker?
Quiet!
Where is the gold?
Move!
- Go, go, go! Forget the tools!
- Come on!
Well, she's in that dress,
is easy to find it!
Friends, our money has been returned.
It was brought by...
Come up here, Young Lady, and tell us your name.
Katakan namamu.
- I'm...
- Wait a second!
- By those men there!
- Move!
Those men are...they are the one that brought back the gold.>
The Queen said that they are undesirable, but
she lied.
They are...great men and thetrue heroes.
With courage, they stopped
the queen's caravan.
and retrieved your gold.
They are the ones that
deserve your thanks.
- You likes the meal?
- Yes, Your Highness. It looks delicious.
I couldn't hear you all the way there.
Everyone commented how a wonderful
dancer you were last night.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I have a question about last night.
There was a girl...
with black hair, beautiful.
I think she's the most beautiful girl
I've ever seen.
- Ever sounds like long time.
- I notice it by my heart.
She's the most beautiful girl in the world.
I agree that we disagree.
Her skin is white ,
her hair is so black...
Her hair is not black, it's dirty.
She's 18 years old, and her skin
never got the sun,
Of course it's good.
I wanted to say that a girl you refer to
was called Snow White.
Snow White?
I acknowledge that the name
fits perfectly.
It's very unfortunate.
The child wasn't always...
Excuse me, you speak about her
in a past tense?
Yes, I am. She is dead.
Dead?
- How?
- Last night in the woods
- Woods is a dangerous place.
- It's terrible.
- You need a moment?
- Yes, thank you. I need a process.
Prince  Alcott, I have a proposition for you.
We're both single adults, rather the same ages...
- I do not think we have the same age.
- I said probably.
The point is that we're talking about us.
Well, people agrees,
Would you do me the honor and be my...
A moment, please!
What?
Excuse my appearance, Highness,
but something unexpected happened.
- Royal taxes have been stolen.
- Stolen, by whom?
- Bandits!
- Bandits?
Yes, Bandits.
- Very intimidating.
- I can't take this anymore.
Enough of these thieves!
Justice must prevail!
Wait.
Wait!
Thank you, Brighton.
This close!
- Meeting. She stole our money.
- But now, people like us.
You can stay.
But we have some conditions
If you're going to live with us,
you have to be one of us.
I have to be a dwarf?
No. It means you have to be a thief.
Remember what I thought about stealing?
- If you steal from the queen?
- You said yourself she's wicked.
- Someone have to stop her.
- Why not you?
Why not us?
- I mean...
- This time I have condition.
Whatever we steal will be returned to the people.
- Minus small commission.
- Butcher!
But she knows nothing about stealing.
We'll teach her.
We'll teach her to believe.
People may think you're tall,
If you are short.
Can be strong even if you are not.
Weakness is only a weakness
when you consider just that.
Never, under any circumstances, give up the high ground.
That one.
Before even draw your sword, you must
make an impression on your enemy.
If you're seen by the way you look...
the battle have won.
People would think of you as sweet.
They don't expect you to fight them.
Use that for your advantage.
Concentrate
Your weapon isn't your only friend.
The environment can be your ally too.
Inception on a battlefield isn't just an option.
You're so cute when you're mad.
But it can make the difference
between victory and defeat.
I'm sorry.
But you deserved it.
It's where we ambushed last time.
Keep your eyes open.
I have to get away from here.
- Ma'am, may I help you?
- Everything's fine, sir, everything is alright.
I just need a...
- It's you!
- I thought you were dead.
- I almost was.
In delivering their values!
Stay behind me.
I'll protect you.
One and a
- You are the bandits?
- You're with the queen.
- You are a traitor.
- And you're a jerk.
Alright, tht's enough.
Stop!
- I can't fight you.
- Why not?
'Cause you're a girl.
I don't fight girls.
I may change my mind.
- The queen did say that you're a little crazy.
- She also assumed I was dead.
See the tree!
The Queen not only robbing
but also manipulating you.
It's absurd.
Things would go well if you and
your friends stop robbing.
Let's take a ride!
You...
Should we help her?
I thought she's okay.
She's doing pretty good on her own.
If you're not trying to stab me,
I might have tried to kiss you.
Everybody is trying then.
- You remember this?
- Yes, remember this?
- Please, forgive me.
- No. Forgive me.
I'm the best.
So you...
Put ??it down.
We're done fighting.
Don't you have learned that?
You throw like a girl.
Why do you have to be so cute?
What?
Well...Well...Prince Alcott.
We must stop meeting like this.
We were ambushed.
The bandits caught us by surprise.i dengan tiba-tiba.
You went into the woods to find the bandits,
and yet the bandits caught you by surprise?
I must admit we were out of skill.
The leader was extremely cruel and cunning, she...
She?
- The bandits' leader is it?
- The bandits's leader is Snow White.
Impossible, sir.
Snow White is dead.
Perhaps she's just someone
who look like Snow White.
Definitely was Snow White.
You're in in the forest, it was dark...
I think we should at least over ourselves at the
possibility,
to someone who looks a lot like the late Snow White.
- It's a fun surprise.
- I agree that we disagree.
- You told me she was dead.
- He said she was dead.
- I'm sure I was dead.
- You said she was mad.
She is mad.
But not as mad as I am,
however.
So which is it she's or dead?
She looked healthy when she and her band of dwarves...
Dwarves?
You said giants?
I...
Giant dwarves.
They're big,
But sometimes small.
- I feel like I've been deceived.
- No. I've been deceived.
I feel...
By God, someone can bring this man
a shirt, so I can concentrate.
Not you, Brighton.
Not you.
I wonder if you misleaded by you or
by Snow.
But I think these events are completely confusing.
Confusing?
A fine word, a grand word
for this situation.
In years to come, people will
look upon the word "confusing"
will give as an example, this afternoon,
when the world knows that a dead girl
is alive and leading around
a bandits of giant dwarves.
And here I was having such a good day!
Mirror mirror on the wall...
Is she really alive?
I was going to tell you,
but I thought it will be more
entertaining let you find out on your own.
I don't understand!
Brighton said that she's finished by the beast.
Brighton told to hurt the victim like all the others.
- I need your magic!
- There's price to use magic.
What is the price you're talking about?
Do you have to be so cryptic?
- I just want her dead!
- So much anxiety.
You should do something about the prince.
Forget Prince, perhaps Baron is more appropriate.
No, I want to marry the prince.
His heart yearned for Snow White.
Use the love potion no 4.
Like I served her father.
You spent it all.
You used it too much.
- I want want Brighton's dead too.
- Don't over react.
If you kill Brighton, you will be without
your executive servant.
You're right.
But we must punish him for lying.
- Give something terrible!
- Use your magic!
You pay the price...
Yes, I know, I paid the price for using magic.
I understand.
Punish him!
Enter.
You wish to see me, Your Highness?
- Please have a drink.
- Thank you, Your Highness. I'm Not really thirsty.
Because...
You are a man in love.
Is that obvious?
I forgive you.
I don't understand, Your Majesty.
I don't.
When I met her in the forest,
she seemed so kind,
And then she shocked me...
Perfect... the word...
- Today...
- Do you care for her?
Snow White is a very rebellious.
- Some would say it is very difficult to contain.
Love can be so confusing.
Yes
I thought I had found my ideal man
by...
He disappeared.
You're right.
We must honor the late King.
- The fallen hero must be remembered.
- Must be...
- No. Gold is my lucky color.
- Sure.
What are you doing?
Master!
Get off me!
Get off!
Love... Puppy?
Puppy Love.
What to do with a dog?
Let's have fun!
You can walk with me to Scotland!
You can play the ball.
And I will bring it back.
- You can tickle my tummy.
- This is the next topic.
- All I want is to marry you.
- Yes Casar.
This, I do.
I will marry you.
Because I love you.
I love the ends of the earth.
I love you till the end of the seven seas
Yes! Yes! You are my master!
Stop it!
Grab!
Go after him!
Go get it!
There are pros and cons.
We need a break!
- Who put that tree there?
- Lord...
Boys, I think
will want to know what I heard at the inn.
- What?
- The Queen's getting marry.
- How? Again?
- It's not good.
- Who?
- With the Baron?
- No.
She's marrying a prince.
- Why would they do that?
- Why would it?
Someone give me the potatoes, please?
When is the wedding?
Tomorrow, down at the lake.
Potatoes, please...
What?
It's a private ceremony.
- What was that?
- Idiot! Do not you see that she loves him?
She loves him?
He ??tried to kill him today.
- Exactly. What do you think love means?
- Do you love when someone gives you potatoes.
I love you, Grub.
- I wanted to hit him.
- Better target.
Someone give me the potatoes?
- Is not someone better go after her?
- No. It's a girl.
- Screaming girls, are no big deal.
- No wonder your wife left you.
- Do not fill the bag...
- Watch your mouth!
I want her killed so much.
- It's black magic!
- Guys...
Guys!
Shoot!
Behind you!
It's coming!
Move! Move!
- Parts I do!
- Look out!
No, Butcher!
Butcher!
Go! Go!
I need help!
- Butcher!
- I'm fine!
Here we go!
Run!
Quick! Quick! Enter!
It's above you!
Move over! Move over!
We must fight back!
Puppets !
Butcher!
Are you ok?
What is he doing?
Is that a custom in Valencia?
Must...
look...
Glorious!
After all it is a special occasion.
How special can it be?
You've been married five times.
Shut up!
Happy face!
I was a cockroach.
It was a nightmare.
I was small and crunchy and
was afraid of the light exposure.
Everyone tried stepping on me!
And then something strange happened.
A grasshopper took advantage of me.
Fascinating, but it's my wedding today
we are not interested in your adventures.
- Suits me up
- But I was...
Suit it.
Out of my way, amateur.
I knew I was still in the same size!
Untie me.
It's time for me to get rich.
Staying rich.
Bring along the sled.
Boys, come here.
Wake up!
Boys, wake up!
- Snow is gone.
- What?
You searched for her in the kitchen?
Probably she left while we slept.
Impossible.
She never just leaves us like that.
- She prepared the breakfast?
- No, but... left a note.
Let's see.
Dear Butcher, Napoleon, Grub, Half Pine,
Wolf, and Chuck Grimm.
I'm so sorry to leave.
I love you all dearly...
All?
Loves everyone?
Read
I love you all dearly...
But I knew
that my presence would harm you.
I thought I was strong enough
to do this, but I'm not.
I'm not like my father wanted I was.
I'm not a leader.
I'll go somewhere far,
where the queen can not find me.
I always remember the time we spent together.
Love, Snow White.
PS: I left a stack of pancakes on the stove
I do not want pancakes,
I want Snow White.
Okay.
Let's see the options, we have to vote.
No.
No meeting and no vote.
Let's go after her now.
Come on, guys!
She can not be far off.
Wolf, you track her.
Snow White...
- Snow White!
- You supposed to let me leave.
No, don't leave us.
You can not quit now.
What about Prince?
- He loves someone else...
- She's right. He does...
- Impossible.
- I don't have a chance with the prince.
Like I've never have a chance against the Queen.
You said that we should fight her because she was mean to us.
We could steal from her,
while not causing any damage.
- It's not what she said.
- I was taking a poetic license.
Snow White, we the seven dwarves
believed that we had no choice in life
but you gave us another choice.
You are strong enough to do that.
- We don't see a girl looking to be strong.
- We see a princess.
- And a leader.
- Our Leader.
- The kingdom needs you.
- I need you.
I mean... We need you.
Who feels like crushing a wedding?
Yes!
Hello!
Glad to see you.
- What were you thinking.
- I just talked to one of his cousins.
Is there.
Excuse me!
- This is a robbery.
- Give us money.
- And clothes.
- No!
- He asked for the clothes?
- Will not do this to me again!
No matter how many times I do it
I still get excited on my wedding day.
Resync by YussiZa
- What's with this kingdom?
- It's outrageous.
- Insulting?
- Your Majesty!
If you can not deal with a few bandits,
is not worthy of being a leader.
The Nobility want you out.
- Excuse me, Baron, what you said...
- Out!
Dismissed! Removed from office!
Okay. Can someone get the prince, please?
- I am afraid he is not here, Your Majesty.
- What?
- Prince has been kidnapped.
- By whom?
Snow White.
If you want someone's dead,
you have to do it yourself.
Take me back to my precious queen!
- Ready! Enough!
- You do not understand!
- Longing for the nectar of her skin...
- Nectar of her skin?
- Who talks like that?
- He must be under a spell.
A spell ?
Seems the style of Queen.
Does anyone know how to break a spell?
My only pain is by being absent from  the queen.
Here you go, buddy.
Does anyone have any more ideas?
I know! I can not believe I
don't think of it sooner.
- A kiss!
- What?
Kiss of true love can undo a spell.
This is the stupidest idea I ever heard.
Well, and boxer's ears
was a great idea!
- She is not kissing anyone!
- Who put you in charge of her lips?
It's final!
Guys!
This is not how I imagine my first kiss...
But...
- I think it's worth a try.
- Wait.
Is this your first kiss?
- We can do better.
- Napoleon!
It's her first kiss!
Don't mess with me on this!
Please don't do it...
No, no, no,
no, no, no
Don't sit, no
Close your eyes.
I can't do it.
I need a little privacy.
Please.
- Oh, I...
- I understand...
I don't want that, but that's okay.
Come back to me.
Please...
- You think she's enjoying herself?
- Yes, I do.
- Grande?
- Yes
Queen...
I told you it would not work!
I am the only one who knows what happens.
Nothing compared to you.
Your lips tasted like strawberries.
How did you do that?
Can you imagine the prince married the queen
for the intire life?
How to marry the queen
the rest of your life?
- I do not like the queen.
- It's true. You were under her spell.
You even wanted the nectar of her skin.
You don't understand!
I long for the Nectar of her skin!
What a bizarre...
Thank you for saving me!
I think when we misjudged you know
and many other unpleasant ways.
I was wrong.
I apologize.
It's ok. You're not stupid,
as I thought.
Butcher!
Is he always like this?
The Beast!
It never come to this side of the woods.
It came for me.
Gentlemen, you are
best fighters for a battle.
- Yes!
- But it's my fight.
- What? Is she just...
- She closed the door.
Snow White!
Unlock the door!
While imprisoned in the castle,
I read a lot.
I read many stories of princes rescuing princesses.
Open the door!
Open the door, Snow White.
- I think it's time to change the ending.
- No, you did everything you could.
Let me save you!
Unlock the door!
Unlock the door, Snow White!
It was a perfect kiss first.
Snow White...
Snow White!
Unlock !
Unlock the door, Snow White!
Back up! Back up!
If you are looking for me,
I'm here!
Yes! Yes...
You?
- What are you doing here?
- Getting fresh air.
Clearing my head...
I don't know if you heard, but...
my groom is stolen!
- You're not afraid of the beast?
- It does what I want.
Did you kill my father?
Dear...
This one will be easy.
I'm stronger than you think.
Die well, Snow White.
You have a good carpenters!
Does anyone have a key?
Idiot.
- I think it's time to fight!
- Yes!
Locked in our own home!
Snow White!
- AND strength!
- Guys.
Guys!
You know we have a copy, right?
You?
What are you doing here?
I figure if I want to die,
has to be with the one I loved.
Go. Go!
Duck!
Snow White!
- Snow White!
- This way!
- Would you lock the door, guys?
- No!
Fight with someone your own size!
The dark magic ruled the land.
The kingdom was turned into icy despair
Queen realized if she'll to remain
the most beautiful in all the land.
Snow have to do what snow does best.
Snow would have to fall.
We have to give this to Snow White.
Give me.
Here, Snow White.
Snow White!
Kill it!
You're ready to pay the price for
using magic?
Who is the guy with the crown?
- Father?
- Snow White.
You're alive!
I can not believe you're alive!
I don't understand...
- You were under the spell of the queen.
- You were child.
I know...
It's a long story.
Who is this young man?
This is the prince who gave
to save the kingdom.
And the bravest soldiers of all
kingdom.
You were good.
Thank you.
But the princess is perfectly
capable of handling it all alone.
However, for your bravery I
will remain eternally grateful.
Tell me how could I repay you?
- With gold.
- A feast...
A girlfriend...
Highness, I want one thing.
Among the privileges of the king,
There is none greater than the power...
of joining two people together
in matrimony.
Prince Alcott, you've found this kingdom in
greed and poverty,
but never strayed,
and entered the battle.
Everyone knows that we owe you much for
your courage and your compatriots
Great gratitude.
Snow White, my daughter,
The kingdom was lucky that in my absence
you're never stopped in believing yourself.
And you became a woman,
I knew you would have always become.
Despite the impossible odds you've faced,
the Queen, and defeated her,
Finally releasing the kingdom from all evil.
Then, by the power vested in me...
by me.
I pronounce you, husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Do I have to say please?
- I always cry at weddings.
- Me too.
Are you single?
Snow White!
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
- Congratulations, my dear.
- Thank you, Mr. Judge.
It would warmed my ancient heart
if you could accept this modest gift.
On your wedding day.
- Very kind of you..
- Just one bite...
And good fortune...
To the fairest of them all.
Ancient before beauty.
It's important to know
when you're been defeated.
Yes...
And it was Snow White's story after all.
END